Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Records WAG.215
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: President's Office Files, 1967-2001.
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - NAACP: NY Branch, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - NAACP: Silent March on Washington, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - NAACP: Voter Registration, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - National Baptist Convention: Labor Roundtable, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - National Black Theater, Inc., 1988 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - National Health Insurance: Single Payer, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - National Labor Committee, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - National Puerto Rican March for Justice, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Negro Labor Committee, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Neponsit Hospital, 1985-1994 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Neponsit Hospital, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Neponsit Hospital: AIDS, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Neponsit Nursing Home, 1992, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - New Afrikan Legal Network, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Newsome, George: Retirement, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - New Voice of New York, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - NYC Budget, 1989-1994 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - NYC Office of Labor Relations: Pay Scales, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - NYC School System: Nurses' Aides, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - New York Consumer Assembly, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - New York Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1986-1991 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - New York Labor for Peace, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - New York Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - New York State AFL-CIO Conference, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - New York State Association of Black and Puerto Rican Legislators, Inc., 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - New York State Association of Black and Puerto Rican Legislators, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - New York State Budget, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New York State Department of Health Conference on Health Care Work Force, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New York State Health Care Campaign, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - New York State Institute for Health and Human Services Seminar, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - New York State Martin Luther King Jr. Commission, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - New York State Public Sector Coalition on Health Benefits, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - New York Times: Letter to the Editor (Jim Butler), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - New Yorkers for Racial and Social Justice, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Nieves, Rievette, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Nigeria: Reception for Maryam Babangida, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Noble, Gil: "Like It Is", 1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Non-Chargeable Educational Leave, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1988-2000 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Cafeteria, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Central Supply, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Health and Safety, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Meetings, 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Members' Complaints, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Montefiore Affiliation, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Needle Disposal, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Rally, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital: Research and Negotiations, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - North General Hospital, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Nuclear Free New York Harbor, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Nurse Aides, 1989, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Nurse Aides: Certification Test (ETS), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Nurse Aides: City-wide Meeting, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Nurse Aides: Federal Certification Requirements, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Nurse Aides: Long-Term Care, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Nurse Aides: Training, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Nurse Recognition Day, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Nurse Training, Undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Nursing Career Ladder Program, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Nursing Home Reform Law, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Nursing Home Reform Law Workshop, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Occupational Safety and Health Administration (OSHA): Bloodborne Disease Standard, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - OSHA Hearings: Safety, Nov 1989 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Office of the Chief Medical Examiner, 1987-1993 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Office of the Chief Medical Examiner: Meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Officers List (L-420), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Operating Room Technicians, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Organizing: General, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Palmer, Russell, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Panama Invasion, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Passports (Africa Trip), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Patient Abuse, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Patient Abuse Seminar, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Patient Care Associates, 1982-1996 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Paul Robeson Theater Benefit, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Pay Scales, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Peace Dividend Campaign, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - People Against Crack, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - People Against Crack Rally, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - PEOPLE Drive, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - People's United Methodist Church, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - People Working For People: TV Talk Show, Undated (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Pharmacy Technicians, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Phelps-Dodge Rally, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Philippines, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Political Action, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Political Action Forms Distribution, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Political Dues Debates, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Presidential Election, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Election: Florida, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Press Release, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Prison Health Committee, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Prison Hospitals, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Prisons: Contracting-out of Health Services, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Privatization, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Progressive Club Raffle, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Psychiatric Social Health Technician Training Program, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Psychiatry Nurse Aide Reception, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Public Employees Federation (NYS) Luncheon, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Publication Department, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Publicity: Clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Public Works Program: Work-Fare, 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Public Works Program: Work-Fare-Butler Testimony, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rico, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Puerto Rico: Hurricane Relief, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Puerto Rico: Mudslide Fund, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Puerto Rican Caucus (Albany), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Puerto Rican Heritage Gala, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Quality of Work Life, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Queens Black/Jewish People to People Project, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Queens Hospital Center, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Queens Hospital Center Policy on Exposure to Blood Fluids, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Queens Hospital Center/Queens General Hospital, 1986-2001 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Queens Women's Network, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - R.J. Reynolds: Cigarettes Aimed at Black Smokers, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Rallies and Demonstrations, 1991-1999 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Rangel, Charles, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Reagan Budget Rally and Nuclear Threat, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Reagan Rally, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Real Estate Transactions (L-420 Inc.), 1994 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Receipts: Expenses, Etc., 1989-1994 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Registered Care Technologists, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Regulated Medical Waste Policy Draft, Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Release Time, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Respiratory Therapy Technicians, 1994-1999 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Respiratory Therapy Technicians: Licensing, Etc., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Restraints Guidelines, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Retraining Grants, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Roberts, Lillian, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Roberts, Lillian: Resignation and Criticism of Cuomo Administration, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Safety Conference, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Salvadoran Hospital Workers, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Save Our City Hospitals: Demonstration at Harlem Hospital, Apr 25, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Save Our Public Hospitals: Breakfast, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Seaview Hospital, 1986-1995 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Seaview Hospital (Staten Island), 2000 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Segundo, R. Belvis, 1990, 2001 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Service Employees International Union, Local 74, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Severance Incentive Program, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Shepard, Peggy, Undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Shop Steward/Chapter Chair: Rights, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Shop Stewards, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Shop Stewards: Meetings, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Sipser, Weinstock, Harper and Dorn, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Slip Lawsuit, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU): AFSCME L-371, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Somebody Cares: A Self-Help Movement, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Smith, Malcolm A., 1991 (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - South Africa, 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - South Africa: A.N.C. Support Conference, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - South Africa Divestment Campaign: Columbia University, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - South Africa: Protests, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Stand For Children (Albany), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - State Funding to Address Hospital Personnel Shortages, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Stress Management, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sullivan, Dennis: Budget Matters, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Summer Camp Registration, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Sunrise Prayer Vigil (Albany), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Supplemental Low-Income Pateint (SLIP) Fund, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Surgical Technician Training Program, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Sydenham NFCC, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Teamsters, Local 237, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Three-Sixty-Four Broadway, 1988-1992 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Tibaldi, Arthur, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Total Care Unit (PIP), Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Total Health Systems: Payoffs, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Trade Union Advisor (Labor Research Association), 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Transitional Jobs Bill: Lee Saunders Testimony, 1992-1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Trester, Michele, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Turkey Certificates, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Turkey Certificates, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Turkey Distribution, Undated, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Turkey Requests, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - TWA Boycott, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Uniform Allowance Meeting, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - UNITE: Laundry Workers, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - United Farm Workers: Grape Boycott, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - United Hospital Fund, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - United Nurses of America: Congress, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - U.S. Health Care, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Uniform Allowance, 1991-1998 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Universal Precaution Procedure, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Upgrade of Titles, Undated (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Urban League, New York, Undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Vanguard Independent Democratic Association, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Voices of Local 420, 1983-1992 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Voter Registration, 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Wakefield Kiwanis Club, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Wapples, Henry, Oct 29, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Watkins, Juanita, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - WBAI, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - WBAI: Speak-out on Budget Cuts, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Webb, James, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Weiner, Grace, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Welfare Reform, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Women's Committee (CLUW) of Local 420, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Women's Conference (AFSCME), 1980-1989 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Women's History Month, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Woodhull Hospital, 1983-1990 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Woodhull Hospital, 1991-2001 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Crisis in Housekeeping, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Cumberland Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Demonstration, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Doctor's Rally, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Doctor's Rally, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Elections, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Woodhull Hospital: Meetings, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Woodley, Ella, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Worker's Defense League, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Worker's Defense League: Honoring Gerald McEntee, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Workfare Employees, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Workplace Violence: Healthcare, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - World Festival of Youth and Students, Undated (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Wurf, Jerry, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Youth Board Employment: Contract, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Series II: Executive Vice-President's Files, 1980-2000.
  - Albanese, Sal, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians, L. 802, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - AFSCME: Butler Campaign, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - AFSCME DC 37, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Delegate Calculations, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Dues Increase, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Finances, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Legal Services Plan, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Legislative Conference, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Lobby Day, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Lobbying Institute, 1996, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - AFSCME DC 37, L.1113 (Finance Employees), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - AFSCME DC 37, L.1251: Leadership Conference, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - AFSCME DC 37, L. 1549, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Minutes and Financial, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - AFSCME DC 37: Proposed Organizing Conference, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME: Health Care Advisory Committee, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - AFSCME: Judicial Panel Report, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Bahamas Hotel…etc., 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Bahamas Hotel Catering Allield Working Union, 1997, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Bargaining, 1995-2000 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Bellevue Hospital, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Bellevue Hospital: Election, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Belvis Diagnostic and Treatment Center, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Berean Baptist Church, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Birthday Calendar, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Black Electorate: Study, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Black History Program, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Black History Forum Coalition, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Black Presidential Candidacy: Study, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Black Women, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Boys and Girls Club of Harlem, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Bronx Municipal Hospital/Jacobi Center, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Bronx Municipal Hospital/Jacobi Center: Health and Safety, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Bronx Central Laundry, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Bronx Central Laundry: Privatization Proposals, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Brooks, Patricia, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Budget (NYS), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Budget Cuts, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Burch, Geneva: Poems, Undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Butler, James: General, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Butler, James: Itinerary, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Cafeterias: Privatization, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Campaign to Save Our Public Hospitals, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Caribbean American Clergy Coalition, 1995 (2000?) (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Catholic New York, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Census, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Chapter Chair Training, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Choir, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Christmas Expenditures, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Citizen Action, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Clinton-Gore Campaign, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, Undated, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - CBTU, Undated, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - CBTU, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - CBTU: Conference, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - CBTU: Convention, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - CBTU: Cruise, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - CBTU: Martin Luther King Convention, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - CBTU: New Jersey Chapter, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - CBTU: New York Chapter, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - CBTU: Resolutions, Undated, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - CBTU: Youth Delegation, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - CLUW, 1984-1985, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Commission on Public Health System, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Conference Attended: List, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Conferences: List, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Constitution (L. 420), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Community Against Pollution, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Coney Island Hospital, 1992-2000 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Cafeteria, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Housekeeping Dept., Undated (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Privatization, 1996-2000 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Problems, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Coney Island Hospital: Sublease, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Conference and Convention Expenses, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Citywide, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Conference, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - DeBow, Louise, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Delia Sigma Theta, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Democratic National Convention, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Dietary Aides, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Domestic Partnership, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Ebenezer Missionary Baptist Church, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Election Committee, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1996, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Elmhurst Hospital, 1992-2000 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Health and Safety, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Hispanic Employees Protests, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Elmhurst Hospital: Sexual Harassment Charges, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Engagement Diary, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - England, Marshall C., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Espada, Pedro (State Senator), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Executive Board (L. 420), 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Executive Board: Legal Report, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Federal Aid to New York City Hospitals, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Fields, Virginia, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Finances (L. 420), 1996-1998 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - First Baptist Church of Crown Heights, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Flushing Hospital, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Friendly Baptist Church, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - General Membership Meeting, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Gore Campaign, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Gospel Choir Concert, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Governeur and Bellevue: Inter-Net, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Governeur Hospital: Election, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Grace Congregational Church of Harlem, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Harlem Hospital, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Harlem Hospital: Election Returns, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Harlem Hospital Protest, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Hayes, Charles, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - HHC, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - HHC: Backfill Vacancies, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - HHC: Community Health Partnership Programs, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - HHC: Early Retirement Incentive, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - HHC: Employee Health Service, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - HHC: Maria Mitchell, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - HHC: Reductions in Bed Count, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - HHC: S.L.I.P. Fund, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Health and Safety, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Health and Safety: Smoke-Free Policy, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Health and Safety: West Nile Virus, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Health Care Environment: Change in, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Health Care: National Trends, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Hill vs. Giuliani, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Hispanic Heritage Month, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Hospital Support Sunday, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - H.E.R.E., Los Angeles, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Hurricane Relief, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Jackson, Jesse, Jr., 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - James, Willie, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Job Seekers, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Jobs with Income Summit, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Jobs with Justice, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Kennedy, Sarah: General, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - King, Bernice A., 1999 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - King Emmanuel Missionary Baptist Church, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Memorial Gospel Concert, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: Poem about by Gloria Bufford, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Kings County Hospital, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Koch, Edward, Undated (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Layoffs, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Leaflet Distribution, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Lincoln Hospital, Undated (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Laundry Workers, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Lincoln Hospital: Problems, 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Local 1199, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Local Staff, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Lucy, William, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Medicaid Cuts, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Memorial Services, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Metropolitan Hospital, 1990-1997 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Cafeteria, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Metropolitan Hospital: Housekeeping, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Morris Brown College Choir, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Mushroom Farm Workers: Rally, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - NAACP, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - National Baptist Convention, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - National Baptist Convention: Labor Relations Dept., 1997 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - National Council of Negro Women, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Neponsit Hospital, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Neponsit Hospital: Election, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - New Canaan Baptist Church, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - New Job Titles Seminar, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - New York Central Labor Council, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - New York Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - New York Coalition for Public Works Jobs, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - New York Jobs with Justice, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - New York City AFL-CIO Convention, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - New York State Public Coalition, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - NYU: Building Trades Protest, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - North Central Bronx Hospital, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Nursing Homes: General, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)